I guess you watched the thumbnail,
right? Yes. With 800 rupees, I will tell
you how you need to get one highaying
client using hot ads lead strategy
inside Meta. Okay. Uh without getting
any delay, let's get into the topic. Hi,
my name is Virat Saudi and people know
me as Hello Viru and I am the founder
and CEO Trader School #1 business school
for freelancing. Let's get started.
So to run ads
you should solve a specific problem
inside specific industry.
Getting my point? So in 2025
the most important thing is you have to
become a specialist than a journalist.
Don't say like hi are you looking for
digital marketing services? I can
provide you that. Nobody will give a
damn about it. If they give any damn
about it also they pay you a very less
amount and you will stuck in a low
paying income forever if you onboard no
knowledge or on low paying claims.
Clear? So first what we need to do is
like for instance I will take an example
of dentists. Imagine my niche is
healthcare and inside that my micro
niche I want to solve or serve dentists.
So what problem can I solve exclusively
for dentists using 800 rupees and
creating hot at lead strategy inside
meta. Let's get started. Okay. So the
first one I'll share my screen. We need
a poster to run the ad, right? We cannot
simply run just like that. So poster add
a good pipe. So the first thing which I
want to tell you is I'm going to divide
this video into
design phase,
copy phase,
add creation stage
and running stage. You getting my point?
So let's go to the first stage which is
design phase. So in the design I'm only
creating a poster. But if you are
serious and want to get more quality
leads and good leads, I want you to mix
this poster with any one to video ads.
Shoot video ads like this. Are you done
this looking to increase your OBS? Then
use this ABCD framework to increase it.
So click on the link below and submit a
form. I will personally get back to you
on a one-to-one call. Something like
that. create a video ad which is more
powerful. So okay so let's key let's get
uh any ad right now you can see my
screen right uh this is my canva
dashboard
just wanted just I'm looking for
something which is good let us give this
first
so let's search for
doctor code. Okay, I've already searched
it.
Or else let's directly search for
dentist
5x
rupees.
I'm just designing the poster right in
front of you.
Okay.
So forward this. Okay. So to just see
the output because I'm thinking right
now in my mind I do not have any. So I'm
just thinking creatively
this is teeth or tooth I don't know
English let's focus on this is tooth
Use TRS
formula.
Let's zoom this a bit.
So example, I can make this more
creative if I have some time. 5x your
op. Hi dental doctor. This is tooth
helping you generate 5x op for you.
Uh so these three can be
used. Very good. Let's do one thing. So
as you are already watching this, let us
take the screenshot
and upload to charge.
You can see the poster, right? I am
creating a ad, but I want something
creative.
So I said 5x your opi dental doctor and
I said this is tooth want to help you
generate 5x but there are three
highlights right above the tooth like
three important things what I can paste
in that three segments so that it can
make meaningful not like randomly we're
posting those three like I'm thinking
like how we can do it to increase 5x
what are the three things that we want
to do it so can you please tell those
three
We have AI, right? Let's ask AI.
You're you're getting my point. I'm
trying to get something more creative in
the ad so the dental doctors especially
pay attention.
So let's focus on the first one
reputation
and second one
showcase
and third one
meta ads. Okay. Okay. This is nice.
Okay. Now what? Oh, this is let us
imagine control AO
agency
example. This is your logo. Now what I
do is like I'll download this.
Yeah, I'll download this
good poster, right? Not bad.
So the design phase is now completed.
Now comes to the copy phase. Okay, which
is the most important thing, right? We
need to write a beautiful copy for the
poster or for the ad to generate more
leads because we've just investing only
800 rupees. That strategy is I want to
tell you I will tell you how you can
break down 800 rupees and get super hot
leads that can close right so sorry it
took time because I did not prepare
previously what poster do I need to
create so I want to teach you from
scratch like so I've created this poster
right now what we are going to do is uh
we'll ask to chat to generate copy uh
thanks for giving it I want you to
generate a meta ad copy for me so that I
Run advertisements targeting dental
doctors. Remember the ad should contain
hook, problem, solution, and the call to
action is book a one-toone call.
Remember in the copy you have to mention
these three things at any cost.
Reputation, fix your online reputation
and the meaning. Show patient smiles and
the solution. Run location based meta
ads and the solution because these are
the three which we mentioned in the
poster, right? They need to know more
clarity about these three before they
booking a onetoone call. So include
them. Now it will give you a pop.
Hit enter.
Are you struggling to get new opies
despite giving best treatment? Problem?
Most dental clinics are losing patient
because of poor treatment but because
they're online not because of poor
treatment not because of online
reputation solution call to action
absolutely great so what I mean to do is
like let's go to the next stage that is
ad creation stage ad execution stage
okay for getting hot leads and last will
be results
so let's create an ad so if you do not
have a ad manager account just click on
new tab and search ads manager and
create a ads manager account inside meta
ads. So click on create. Now what
exactly you need to do is like click on
leads. Click on continue.
Name this like dental doctors.
Okay. And budget 200. What? What is
this? Where you said 800 rupees. No,
we'll spend only 200 rupees per day for
the next 4 days. Not 800 rupees on a
single day. Okay. So second click on
next.
So instant forms that is what we need
and the page I've already selected and
now show more settings
show more controls because we need more
controls further limit your ad because I
want to do it manual instead of AI so
switch that up so what I need to do is
like doctors generally from maybe let's
target 25 to 44
or let's say 54.
Okay. So the audience uh I don't have
any existing audience. Let's build a
detailed targeting inside the detail
targeting. You can pause this video and
uh just copy paste exactly what I'm
saying.
We'll focus dentist
enough more than enough because we have
a limited budget and we don't want
location entire India. I'm from
Hyderabad so I pick Hyderabad. So
wherever you are in the city you can
pick that city. It could be tier one,
tier 2, tier three city, any city is any
city is fine. Okay. Now what we need to
do is like let's go to and also further
let's narrow it down further. Who know
who is knows or looking for digital
marketing
better?
It is fine. Okay. Now what we need to do
is
click on next.
Now whatever the poster we have designed
we'll upload that poster.
Setup creative
not video ad upload a image ad
upload
users. I like this poster you know this
is good one.
Click on next.
So here is a primary text which we need
to copy from
meta which has given
copy and paste. Make sure you remove
this.
Okay. and also problem
and uh solution.
Okay. And call to action.
That's it. Now what we need to do is
like
book a
free onetoone call.
This is the headline. Okay. Now click on
next. Skip and continue and done.
Boom. Your ad is ready. So the next
thing which we need to work on is the
form.
So many people what they do is like they
collect name, email and phone number.
That's it. They think like they've
generated a good lead. No, you need to
ask more questions. So if you observe my
trader school, if you're joining for a
one-toone mentorship or anything, we'll
ask a set of questions, right? We don't
simply ask name, email, and phone
number. You're getting my point. By the
way, as the topic comes, if you're
looking for a one-to-one mentorship, I
have given a free training on what
exactly onetoone mentorship will look
like and what exact mistake freelancers
are doing. So I will give a link below
in the description or in the pin
comments. You can watch that free
training to get to know what exact
onetoone mentorship will look like.
Okay, see you. Now let's create a form.
I already have one form which is hot
lead. So I'll duplicate that and I'll
show you. Okay. So here you see the form
type. Always keep higher intent because
you're collecting leads inside meta. You
are not redirecting to landing page.
Inside meta, you are collecting ads,
leads, I'm sorry. Okay. So, click on
higher intent and click on next. Here
you see get AI powered marketing
strategy within 1 hour here.
Uh we'll keep like book a free onetoone
call now.
Okay. You can always uh copy
this one or anything. You can paste it
in the description.
Okay. So you can create a new
description as well. Instead of copy
pasting what we have already shown in
the ad, you can create one more using
AI. I've already given how to create. So
click on next. Here comes the game.
Okay. What is your budget for marketing
services? If a dental client said no
budget, do you think that they will pay
you? Do you think that they will become
your client? That means you're
eliminating junk leads to the form
itself. If somebody said 10k to 220k, if
your pricing is between this, you can go
with them. If the somebody said 30k and
above, 20k and above, that's where you
will really find the high paying
clients. And here you see what is your
dental clinic.
Okay. Why do you need marketing for your
business currently? Okay. They need to
give how soon you need it. They need to
write. If they like why do you need
marketing for your business currently?
Huh? Just like that. I I love marketing.
I need leads. If somebody has given
oneliner answers, one word answers, you
can probably think that they are also
not good leads. If somebody given you
your real problem
and how soon they need it, if they say
immediately,
you're going to catch the new hot lead.
Okay? So here you see and then you need
to ask name, email, phone number and
click on next and click on next and
click on next. Ending screen you can
give a calendarly appointment link. You
just simply type Calendarly.
Okay, this is free. After they filling
the form in the end screen, okay, I'll
show go to website. Don't leave this
place before you book a free 1:1 AI
marketing consultation
call with us. Okay, that means they will
see the ad,
they will fill the form and the last
stage which I want to tell results for a
booking. So then they will click once
after they submit they'll click here
book a consultation call here and they
will go to Calendarly and they will
select an appointment whenever they are
free
without calling
without burning out with just 800 rupees
clients are landing on your onetoone
meeting.
Isn't it beautiful?
So if you like this video, like it and
share it with your freelancing friends
and comment on what topics do you want
me to cover in the upcoming videos so
that I will create exact videos on the
same. Considering subscribing if you
like my content, you can watch the
previous videos whatever I put so far.
If you liked it, if you got value,
consider subscribing and turn on the
bell notification. See you by the next
video.